

Personal

Name

Navin Hariharan

Address

Sri Ramachandra Villa, 6/8, Lakshmi nagar 10th street, Nanganallur 600061 Chennai

Phone number +917305574234

Email

navin@navin-hariharan.com

Date of birth 23-02-2003

Nationality Indian

Website

https://navin-hariharan.com/

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/navin-hariharan/

Interests

Coding

Travelling

Video Games

Watching Movies

Listening to Music

Languages

English

Fluent

Tamil Native

Navin Hariharan

With a unique passion for technology that drives me, I have accumulated more thar <u>8 years</u> of experience in the **cybersecurity** domain. In addition to this, I have also accrued <u>2 years</u> of knowledge in a relatively newer field such as **Artificial Intelligence**. I head the top managerial level with all executive powers and responsibilities as the <u>CEO</u> of **CyberHakz Pvt. Ltd**. and <u>Director</u> of **Alfa Global Wealth Advisors Pvt. Ltd** I have learned many tools and programming languages such as

Python, SQL, Stable Diffusion, FLUX, OLLAMA and much more. As a fun fact, I happen to love coding, listening to music and also enjoy driving o stressful situations

Work experience

Founder/CEO Mar 2021 - Present

CYBERHAKZ PRIVATE LIMITED, Tamil Nadu, India

Being the **CEO** of <u>CyberHakz Pvt. Ltd.</u> I guide the company and manage operations. I assure top security methods. I also team up for solutions and give our group ideas. I make important choices and support us in growing.

Director Mar 2021 - Present

Sep 2020 - Sep 2024

Jun 2019 - Mar 2020

Jun 2017 - Mar 2018

ALFA GLOBAL WEALTH ADVISORS PRIVATE LIMITED, Tamil Nadu, Chennai

Education and Qualifications

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science and Engineering

Ponnaiyah Ramajayam Institute of Science & Technology (PRIST), Thanjavur

Central Board of Secondary Education 12th

NARAYANA E-TECHNO SCHOOL - POONAMALLEE, Chennai

Scored **63.60**%

Central Board of Secondary Education 10th

NARAYANA E-TECHNO SCHOOL - PALLAVARAM, Chennai

Scored **58.80**%

Skills

Programming: Python

Artificial Intelligence Tools

Linux

SQL

Al Art

Achievements

- CERTIFIED ETHICAL HACKER -EC-COUNCIL ECC8513964720
- CYBERSECURITY SUMMER INTERNSHIP -GURUGRAM POLICE Jun 2020
- AWARENESS CAMPAIGN Sairam Institutions 2019
- CERTIFICATE OF PARTICIPATION -Kyrion Technologies Feb 2020
- CERTIFICATE OF PARTICIPATION Cybher Sep 2020
- CERTIFICATE OF APPRECIATION SHERLOCK INSTITUTE OF FORENSIC SCIENCE- Sep 2020